

DHARANIKUMAR K

FULL STACK DEVELOPER



CONTACT



Phone

+91-9952638437



Email

dharanfsd@gmail.com



Address

Dusi, Kancheepuram, Tamilnadu



MY SKILLS

- O HTML
- O CSS
- O BOOTSTRAP
- JAVASCRIPT
- REACT JS
- NODEJS
- EXPRESS JS
- MONGODB



SOCIAL MEDIA

PORTFOLIO

HTTPS://DHARANPORTFOLIO.NET LIFY.APP/

() LINKEDIN

HTTPS://WWW.LINKEDIN.COM/IN/ DHARANIKUMARKFSD/

GITHUB

HTTPS://GITHUB.COM/KDHARANI KUMAR



PROFILE INFO

I'm a Mechanical Engineering & MBA Graduate. I have 5 years of experience in the Automobile Industries Quality Department. Now I have to change my career to the Software Industry. So I did the Complete Full Stack Developer (MERN) Course.

Cours

EDUCATION

\bigcirc	Diploma In Automobile	2009-2011
	Engineering	
	Dusi Polytechnic College, Dusi	

\odot	B.E - Mechanical Engineering	2013-2016
	Arulmigu Meenakshi Amman College	
	of Engineering AMACE	
	Vadamavandhal-Kancheepuram	

\bigcirc	MBA - Supply Chain Management	2018-2019
	University of Madras - Chennai	

CERTIFICATION

Quality Trainee

\bigcirc	Full Stack Development (MERN)	2022-2023
	Guvi - Chennai	



(3)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Hyundai Mohis - Chennai

	rryundar Mobis - Onemiai	
③	Quality Engineer Rockman - Cheyyar	2016-2018
③	Quality Engineer TVS Sundaram Clayton - Chennai	2018-2019
③	Entrepreneur STARFLIT- Dusi, Kancheepuram	2019-Till Now

2011-2013

MY ACHIEVEMENT

- Reduce the Rejection by 10% to 3% by process optimization in HPDC along with product design.
- O Conduct TS 16949: 2002 System Internal Audit, MRM.